Trapped behind enemy lines. A whole army after
him... And only one man can save him.
Bat★21 is a action, war, drama film directed by Peter Markle.
Iceal "Ham" Hambleton is a weapons countermeasures expert and when his aircraft is
shot over enemy territory the Air Force very much wants to get him back.
Hambleton knows the area he's in is going to be carpet-bombed but a
temporary shortage of helicopters causes a delay.
Working with an Air Force reconnaissance pilot, Capt.
Bartholomew Clark, he maps out an escape route.
Lt. Col. Iceal Hambleton, played by Gene Hackman.
Capt. Bartholomew Clark, played by Danny Glover.
Col. George Walker, played by Jerry Reed.
Ross Carver, played by David Marshall Grant.
Sgt. Harley Rumbaugh, played by Clayton Rohner.
Major Jake Scott, played by Erich Anderson.
In the film industry, unsimulated sex is the presentation of sex scenes in which actors
genuinely perform the depicted sex acts, rather than simulating them.
Although it is ubiquitous in films intended as
pornographic, it is very uncommon in other films.
At one time in the United States, such scenes were restricted by law and
self-imposed industry standards such as the Motion Picture Production Code.
Films showing explicit sexual activity were confined to privately
distributed underground films, such as stag films or "porn loops".
In the 1960s, social attitudes about sex began to shift, and sexually
explicit films were decriminalized in many countries.
With movies such as Blue Movie by Andy Warhol, mainstream movies began
pushing the boundaries of what was presented on screen.
Notable examples include two of the eight Bedside-films and the six Zodiac-films from the 1970s, all of which were produced in Denmark and had many
pornographic sex scenes, but were nevertheless considered mainstream films, all having mainstream casts and crews and premiering in mainstream cinemas.
The last of these films, Agent 69 Jensen i Skyttens tegn, was made in 1978.
From the end of the 1970s until the late 1990s it was rare to see hardcore scenes in mainstream cinema, but this changed with the success of Lars von Trier's The Idiots (1998), which heralded a wave
of art-house films with explicit content, such as Romance (1999), Baise-moi (2000), Intimacy (2001), Vincent Gallo's The Brown Bunny (2003), and Michael Winterbottom's 9 Songs (2004).
Some simulated sex scenes are sufficiently realistic that critics mistakenly believe
they are real, such as the cunnilingus scene in the 2006 film Red Road.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, vietnam, based on novel or book.
The tone is emotional.